<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- generator="Joomla! - Open Source Content Management" -->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Careers</title>
		<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
		<link>https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:08:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<generator>Joomla! - Open Source Content Management</generator>
		<atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career?format=feed&amp;type=rss"/>
		<language>en-gb</language>
		<item>
			<title>ICT and Digital Media Intern</title>
			<link>https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career/117-ict-and-digital-media-intern</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career/117-ict-and-digital-media-intern</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Location: Lodwar</strong><br><strong>Type: Full-time</strong><br><strong>About Us: </strong><span style="font-size: 1rem;">SERYEETAAB KAA CULTURAL HERITAGE ORGANIZATION (STK) (STK) is a community-focused organization advocating for </span><span style="font-size: 1rem;">social, economic, cultural, environmental, and territorial justice in the Greater Turkana Basin. </span><span style="font-size: 1rem;">We are seeking a motivated and creative individual to join our team as an</span><strong style="font-size: 1rem;"> ICT and Digital Media Intern.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Role Summary:</strong> This dynamic role combines digital storytelling, communications, ICT, and administrative expertise. The ideal candidate is a creative problem-solver, tech-savvy, and highly organized individual, with a passion for impactful storytelling and supporting organizational efficiency.<br><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong><br><strong>Digital Media and ICT</strong></p>
<p style="padding-left: 40px;">• Plan and create multimedia content, including photography, videography, and graphic design.<br>• Produce engaging digital content for social media, the website, newsletters, and reports.<br>• Maintain an organized archive of digital assets for easy retrieval.<br>• Troubleshoot and manage ICT tools, ensuring smooth communication and operations.<br>• Support digital platforms and provide solutions for enhanced online engagement.</p>
]]></description>
			<category>Careers</category>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Energy and Climate Fellow</title>
			<link>https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career/116-energy-and-climate-fellow</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career/116-energy-and-climate-fellow</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Energy and Climate Fellow<br></strong>SERYEETAAB KAA CULTURAL HERITAGE ORGANIZATION (STK) (FOLT), is a grassroots organization that works with and on behalf of the communities within the greater Turkana basin to demand their collective social, economic, environmental, cultural and territorial rights. Recognizing the anti-patriarchal struggle is a vision expressed in all areas of our work. Our mission is to; address socio-economic inequality; demand <br>environmental justice; secure land and territorial rights; seek a social justice framework to addressing energy justice and climate change; and provide for women led community advocacy.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><br><strong>What are we looking for?</strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong> </strong>STK’ is seeking a passionate Energy and Climate Fellow. This position provides a unique opportunity to develop strategic advocacy for energy and climate justice. Working with colleagues and in collaboration with diverse partners, the fellow will identify emerging threats and opportunities, develop policy solutions, and execute multi-faceted advocacy initiatives to ensure maximum impact. <br>S/he will support coordination of STK's efforts of advancing Climate and Energy Justice through designing and implementing initiatives that promote community-led climate resilience, equitable energy access and just transition. S/he will be integral in organizing community outreaches, managing projects, developing partnerships and advocating for policy changes through evidence-based advocacy and participatory methods.</p>
]]></description>
			<category>Careers</category>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Knowledge Management &amp; Learning Coordinator</title>
			<link>https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career/115-knowledge-management-learning-coordinator</link>
			<guid isPermaLink="true">https://stk.example/hope/index.php/get-involved/career/115-knowledge-management-learning-coordinator</guid>
			<description><![CDATA[<p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Job Title: Knowledge Management &amp; Learning Coordinator</strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Location: Remote with frequent travels</strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Term: One- year</strong></p>
<p class="MsoNormal">Reports to: Media &amp; Communications Lead/ Team Lead</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"> STK is currently seeking qualified candidates for a Knowledge Management and Learning fellow who will work part-time with the Media and Communications Lead under the direction of the Director. STK is improving its knowledge management and learning systems to stimulate organizational knowledge and learning. Over the next year, STK is focused on:</p>
<ol>
<li class="MsoListParagraphCxSpFirst">Building an Ateker knowledge and learning platform</li>
<li class="MsoListParagraphCxSpMiddle">Promoting an organizational culture where sharing knowledge and learning is expected and celebrated</li>
<li class="MsoListParagraphCxSpMiddle">Streamlining knowledge management-related policies and processes</li>
<li class="MsoListParagraphCxSpLast">Support updates to and rationalization of our knowledge systems</li>
</ol>
<p class="MsoNormal">This fellowship is an exciting opportunity for someone with a background and interest in knowledge management, organizational learning, and international development.</p>
<p class="MsoNormal"><strong>Roles &amp; Responsibilities:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>As a Knowledge Management and Learning fellow, you will play a crucial role in promoting an organizational culture where sharing knowledge is not just expected, but celebrated. Your efforts will be instrumental in fostering a collaborative environment where everyone's insights contribute to our collective success.]]></description>
			<category>Careers</category>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
